Guide to the Stanford University, Stanford Repertory Theatre, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - Individual Production Notebooks (Box 8)
    - ANTONY AND CLEOPATRA, 1966-67 (Box 8)
    - THE CHERRY ORCHARD, 1966-67 (Box 8)
    - INADMISSABLE EVIDENCE, 1966-67 (Box 8)
    - THE GOOD WOMAN OF SETZUAN (Box 8)
    - Theater At The Museum, MFA Projects, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - THE CAVERN, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - COCK A DOODLE (Box 8)
    - THE INSPECTOR GENERAL, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - Undergraduate Productions, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - CANDAULES, COMMISSIONER, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - THERE IS A MEETING PLACE - OUT AT SEA, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - VARIOUS - 1967-1968 SEASON, 1967-68 (Box 8)
    - CUCHULAIN, TCR, FUNNY THING, 1968-69 (Box 8)
    - SEASON, 1968-69 (Box 8)
    - ANDROCLES AND THE LION, 1969-70 (Box 8)
    - THE ICEMAN COMETH, 1969-70 (Box 8)
    - THE CAGE, 1969-70 (Box 8)
    - THE DRUMS OF SNOW, 1969-70 (Box 8)
  - Individual Production Notebooks and Albums, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    Notebooks contain programs and press clippings from proouctions of the 1969-70 (last) season. Albums contain pictures from individual productions as labelled.
    - SHADOW OF HEROES, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - THE UNKNOWN SOLDIER AND HIS WIFE, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - WAlTING FOR GODOT, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - THE WINTER' S TALE, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - SEASON, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - Class Projects - Sale, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - CANDAULES, COMMISSIONER (Box 9)
    - THE CAVERN (Box 9)
    - COCK A DOODLE DANDY (Box 9)
    - THE ICEMAN COMETH, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - SHADOW OF HEROES, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - THE DRUMS OF SNOW, 1969-70 (Box 9)
    - THE UNKNOWN SOLDIER AND HIS WIFE, 1969-70 (Box 9)
  - Albums and Scrapbooks, 1964-67 (Box 10)
    Albums contain pictures from individual productions, but are not labelled. Scrapbooks contain press clippings for the SRT and for individual performances, 1964-67.
  - Scrapbooks, 1965-68 (Box 11)
    Scrapbooks contain press clippings for the SRT and for individual performances, 1965-68.
  - Production Books (Box 12)
    - a. All's Well That Ends Well, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - b. Antony and Cleopatra, 1966-67 (Box 12)
    - c. Canduales, Commissioner (Box 12)
    - d. The Cavern, 1967-68 (Box 12)
    - e. The Chairs & The Questions, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - f. The Cherry Orchard, 1966-67 (Box 12)
    - g. Cock-A-Doodle Dandy (Box 12)
    - h. Good Woman of Setzuan, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - i. Inadmissable Evidence, 1966-67 (Box 12)
    - j. Man is Man (Box 12)
    - k. Prometheus Bound, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - l. Scoundrel Scapin, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - m. Shadow of Heroes (Box 12)
    - n. The Skin of our Teeth, 1965-66 (Box 12)
    - o. A Slight Ache & Out at Sea, 1966-67 (Box 12)